A Guide to the Virginia Commission on State Governmental Management Records, 1973-1978
Library of Virginia
- Office of the Lieutenant Governor, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Commission on Local Debt, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Marine Resources Commission, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Virginia Institute of Marine Science, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Dept. of Military Affairs, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Milk Commission, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Board of Mine Examiners, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Virginia State Office of Minority Business Enterprise, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Division of Motor Vehicles, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- Division of Motor Vehicles, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- Museum of Fine Arts, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- Virginia Outdoors Foundation, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Commission of Outdoor Recreation, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Division of Personnel, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Virginia Port Authority, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Dept. of Property Records and Insurance, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Virginia Public School Authority, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Virginia Public Telecommunications Council, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Dept. of Purchase and Supply, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Rehabilitative School Authority, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Virginia Safety and Health Codes Commission, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Science Museum of Virginia, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Virginia School at Hampton, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Secretaries, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Soil and Water Conservation Commission, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Office of Special Programs, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- State Corporation Commission, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Division of State Planning and Community Affairs, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Dept. of State Police, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Commission on Status of Women, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Virginia Supplemental Retirement System, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Dept. of Taxation, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Letter to Agency Heads (example), Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Dept. of the Treasury, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- Treasury Board, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Virginia Truck and Ornamentals Research Station, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- Commission for the Visually Handicapped, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- Dept. of Vocational Rehabilitation, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- Office on Volunteerism, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- Water Control Board, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- Water Research Center, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- Dept. of Welfare, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 32)
- Overview of the Organization of the Virginia State Government- The Establishment of an Appropriate Climate to Maximize Current Effectiveness and Achieve Future Improvements of Service, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- State Reps papers, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- State Agency group report, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Group of Eight, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Notes, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Press releases, 1974-1978 (Box 29)
- Public hearings, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Public hearings, 1975 December 1-5 (Box 29, Folder 2-3)
- Public hearings, 1975 January 7 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Public hearings, 1976 August 2-3 (Box 29, Folder 5-6)
- Public hearings, 1976 August 2-3 (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
- Statements, Administration and Finance, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Statements, Commerce and Resource, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Statements, Education, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Statements, Misc., 1976 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Statements, Human Affairs, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Statements, Transportation and Public Safety, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Statements, State Corporation Commission, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Public hearings, 1976 November-December (Box 30, Folder 10-11)
- Public hearings, 1976 November 9-12 (Box 31, Folder 1-3)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Accountability, 1973-1978 (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Alcohol and Drug Abuse Control, 1973-1978 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Attorney General, 1973-1978 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Executive Management, 1973-1978 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, State Administration of Higher Education, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Education-Shaner's report, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Education- Education Unit Gets Power, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Education- The Changing Nature of the School Superintendency, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Education, Should stats have secretaries of Education?, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Executive Orders, 1973-1978 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Federal budgetary reform, 1973-1978 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Finances, 1973-1978 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, General, 1973-1978 (Box 33, Folder 1-3)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Growth in Government, 1973-1978 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Role of Government, 1973-1978 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Governor, 1973-1978 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Health, 1973-1978 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Human Affairs, 1973-1978 (Box 34, Folder 3-4)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Information system, 1973-1978 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Legislative Clearance, 1973-1978 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Legislation, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Material for 1977 Session, 1973-1978 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Carter Lowance letter, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Mailing list, 1973-1978 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Misc. correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Personnel, 1973-1978 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Privacy and Security, 1973-1978 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Program structure draft, 1973-1978 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Public hearings, 1976 August 2-3 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Research materials, 1973-1978 (Box 36, Folder 2-3)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Reorganization, 1973-1978 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Maurice Rowe letters, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 5-6)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Support services, 1973-1978 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, Transportation, 1973-1978 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Patrick McSweeney, Research files, University liaison, 1973-1978 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Administration and Finance, 1973-1978 (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Agriculture, 1973-1978 (Box 37, Folder 3-5)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Agricultural Product Commission, 1973-1978 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Art Commission, 1973-1978 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Arts and Humanities, 1973-1978 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Automated Data Processing, 1973-1978 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Aviation, 1973-1978 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Boards, 1973-1978 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Budget, 1973-1978 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Commission Finances, 1973-1978 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Computer Resources, 1973-1978 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Conservation, Recreation, and Historic Preservation, 1973-1978 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Corrections, Dept. of, 1973-1978 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Education, 1973-1978 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Education and Cultural Affairs, 1973-1978 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Education, Sec. of, 1973-1978 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Employment and Expenditures, 1973-1978 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Enforcement, 1973-1978 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Enforcement, 1973-1978 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Employment Information, 1973-1978 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Environmental Management, 1973-1978 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Air and Water Analysis, 1973-1978 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Executive Management, 1973-1978 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Expenditure Information, 1973-1978 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Financial Statements, 1973-1978 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Information on Federal Agencies, 1973-1978 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Freedom of Information Act, 1973-1978 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Government role, 1973-1978 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Health, Dept. of, 1973-1978 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Sen. Hopkins, 1973-1978 (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Housing and Community Development, 1973-1978 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Human Affairs, 1973-1978 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Human Resources, 1973-1978 (Box 40, Folder 5-7)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Industrial Development and Tourism, 1973-1978 (Box 40, Folder 8-9)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Industrial Development and Tourism, 1973-1978 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Intergovernmental Affairs, 1973-1978 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Legislation proposed, 1973-1978 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Legislation, HB 1628, 1973-1978 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Legislation, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 6-8)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Legislation, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Legislation, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Marine and Wildlife, 1973-1978 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Medicaid, 1973-1978 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Milk Commission, 1973-1978 (Box 42, Folder 5-6)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Misc., 1973-1978 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Natural Resources, 1973-1978 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Organizational Impact Rule, 1973-1978 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Originals, 1973-1978 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Press Conference, 1977 May 2 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Public Hearings, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Public Safety, 1973-1978 (Box 43, Folder 5-6)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Rehabilitative Services, 1973-1978 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Resource Personnel, 1973-1978 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, State Authorities, 1973-1978 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, State Expenditures, 1973-1978 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, State Corporation Commission, 1973-1978 (Box 44, Folder 3-8)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Taxation, Dept. of, 1973-1978 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Division of Motor Vehicles, 1973-1978 (Box 44, Folder 10-12)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, State Mandated Programs, 1973-1978 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Telecommunications, 1973-1978 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Third interim report and budget, 1973-1978 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Traffic records study, 1973-1978 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Transportation, Governor's Council on, 1973-1978 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Transportation proposals, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Traffic highway safety, 1973-1978 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Truck and Ornamentals research, 1973-1978 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Visually handicapped, 1973-1978 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, Volunteerism, 1973-1978 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Kenneth Golden, Research files, War Veterans claims, 1973-1978 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Traffic records system study, Final report, 1976 March (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Traffic records system study, Executive management and the Highway Fund, 1973-1978 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Traffic records system study, Correspondence, Incoming, 1973-1978 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Traffic records system study, Correspondence, Outgoing, 1973-1978 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Traffic records system study, Carrington Williams, 1973-1978 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Traffic records system study, Hiram Johnson, 1973-1978 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Traffic records system study, Senator Hopkins, 1973-1978 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Traffic records system study, Jane Cromartie, 1973-1978 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Traffic records system study, Management Review Committee, 1973-1978 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Traffic records system study, TAPS Agencies Meetings, 1973-1978 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Traffic records system study, Personnel, 1973-1978 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Traffic records system study, Project accounts, 1973-1978 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Traffic records system study, Travel expense, 1973-1978 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Traffic records system study, Miscellaneous, 1973-1978 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Traffic records system study, Annual meeting, 1976 January (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Traffic records system study, Woods Hole Conference, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Traffic records system study, Appropriations Committee, 1973-1978 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Traffic records system study, Commission Bills, 1973-1978 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Traffic records system study, House Bills, 1973-1978 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Traffic records system study, House Roads Committee, 1973-1978 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Traffic records system study, Senate Bills, 1973-1978 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Traffic records system study, Oregon Bottle Bill, 1973-1978 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Traffic records system study, Recommendations and legislation, 1973-1978 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Traffic records system study, Minutes, 1973-1978 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Traffic records system study, Traffic records, 1973-1978 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Traffic records system study, General reports, 1973-1978 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Traffic records system study, Metro, 1973-1978 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Traffic records system study, Transportation safety, 1973-1978 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Traffic records system study, Rail transportation, 1973-1978 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Traffic records system study, Land use seminar, 1973-1978 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Traffic records system study, Criminal justice training in Virginia, 1973-1978 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Traffic records system study, TRB reports, 1973-1978 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Traffic records system study, Mitre Corp., 1973-1978 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Traffic records system study, Center for auto safety, 1973-1978 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Traffic records system study, Manpower Management, Committee on, 1973-1978 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Traffic records system study, Committee on Manpower Management, Minutes, 1973-1978 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Traffic records system study, Annual Highway Research Board Meeting, 1973 January (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Traffic records system study, Management Review Committee, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Traffic records system study, Manpower Management Workshop, 1974 August (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Traffic records system study, Committee on Manpower Management, 1973-1978 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Traffic records system study, Summer meeting, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Traffic records system study, Manpower Management Committee, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Traffic records system study, Management Review Committee, 1973-1978 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Traffic records system study, Committee on Planning and Administration of Transportation Safety, 1973-1978 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Traffic records system study, Manpower Management Workshop, 1973-1978 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Traffic records system study, Conference, 1975 January (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Traffic records system study, Committee on Manpower Management, Vol. I, 1973-1978 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Traffic records system study, Committee on Manpower Management, Vol. II, 1973-1978 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Traffic records system study, Mississippi Management Seminar, 1973 March (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Traffic records system study, Citizens participation in Transportation Planning, 1973-1978 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Research materials, Agricultural Product Commissions, 1973-1978 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Research materials, Automated Data Processing, 1973-1978 (Box 52, Folder 2-5)
- Research materials, Bibliography, 1973-1978 (Box 53)
- Research materials, Boards and Commissions, 1973-1978 (Box 53, Folder 2-4)
- Research materials, Budget Execution-Control, 1973-1978 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Research materials, Budget, Gross Limitations, 1973-1978 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Research materials, Budget, Program Budgeting Training, 1973-1978 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Research materials, Budget, Zero-base Budgeting, General, 1973-1978 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Research materials, Budget, Zero-base Budgeting, Virginia, 1973-1978 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Research materials, Budget, 1973-1978 (Box 54, Folder 4-6)
- Research materials, Capital Outlay, 1973-1978 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Research materials, Commission information, 1973-1978 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Research materials, Commission meeting, 1976 Dec. 15 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Research materials, Commission press releases, 1973-1978 (Box 55, Folder 3-4)
- Research materials, Definitions, 1973-1978 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Research materials, Education, 1973-1978 (Box 55, Folder 6-8)
- Research materials, Education, 1973-1978 (Box 56, Folder 1-6)
- Research materials, Education, State Council of Higher, 1973-1978 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Research materials, Election Analysis, 1973-1978 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Research materials, Emergency Preparedness, 1973-1978 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Research materials, Finances, State Government, 1973-1978 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Research materials, Finances, 1973-1978 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Research materials, Human Affairs, 1973-1978 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Research materials, Human Services, 1973-1978 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Research materials, Human Services, Legislation, Minnesota, 1973-1978 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Research materials, Independent Boards, 1973-1978 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Research materials, Lt. Governor, 1973-1978 (Box 58, Folder 3-6)
- Research materials, Legislation, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 1-3)
- Research materials, Licensure, 1973-1978 (Box 59, Folder 4-6)
- Research materials, Licensure, 1973-1978 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Research materials, Management, 1973-1978 (Box 60, Folder 2-5)
- Research materials, Milk Commission, 1973-1978 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Research materials, Miscellaneous, 1973-1978 (Box 61, Folder 2-6)
- Research materials, Miscellaneous, 1973-1978 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Research materials, Natural Resources, 1973-1978 (Box 62, Folder 2-6)
- Research materials, General Assembly bills of interest to the Commission, 1977-1978 (Box 63, Folder 1-3)
- Research materials, Environment, 1973-1978 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Research materials, Organizational principles, 1973-1978 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Research materials, Personnel, 1973-1978 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Research materials, Personnel, 1973-1978 (Box 65, Folder 1-5)
- Research materials, Personnel, 1973-1978 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Research materials, Personnel, Salaries, 1973-1978 (Box 66, Folder 2-8)
- Research materials, Preliminary report, 1973-1978 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Research materials, Principles, 1973-1978 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Research materials, Program structure materials, 1973-1978 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Research materials, Position papers, 1973-1978 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Research materials, Purchasing, 1973-1978 (Box 67, Folder 5-8)
- Research materials, Reorganization study process, 1973-1978 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Research materials, Articles, 1973-1978 (Box 68, Folder 1-2)
- Research materials, Services integration, 1973-1978 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Research materials, Social services, 1973-1978 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Research materials, Needs of young children, 1973-1978 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Research materials, Unmet needs, 1973-1978 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Research materials, Society needs and program structure, 1973-1978 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Research materials, Insurance, 1973-1978 (Box 69, Folder 1-5)
- Research materials, Bureau of banking, 1973-1978 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Research materials, SCC, Public utilities legislation, 1973-1978 (Box 70, Folder 2-3)
- Research materials, SCC, Public service taxation, 1973-1978 (Box 70, Folder 4-5)
- Research materials, SCC, Securities, 1973-1978 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Research materials, SCC, Securities, 1973-1978 (Box 71, Folder 1-3)
- Research materials, Division of Aeronautics, 1973-1978 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Research materials, Federal regulatory agency, 1973-1978 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Research materials, SCC, 1973-1978 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Research materials, SCC, Executive management, 1973-1978 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Research materials, Past studies, 1973-1978 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Research materials, Articles, 1973-1978 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Research materials, SCC, 1973-1978 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Research materials, Statutory powers and duties of all agencies, 1973-1978 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Research materials, Dept. of Agriculture and Economic Development, 1973-1978 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Research materials, Dept. of Commerce, 1973-1978 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Research materials, Dept. of Corrections, 1973-1978 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Research materials, Dept. of Emergency Preparedness, 1973-1978 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Research materials, Dept. of Game and Inland Fisheries, 1973-1978 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Research materials, Dept. of Health, 1973-1978 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Research materials, Dept. of Public Safety Planning, 1973-1978 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Research materials, Dept. of Labor and Industry, 1973-1978 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Research materials, Dept. of Ports, Railways, and Waterways, 1973-1978 (Box 73, Folder 10)
- Research materials, Dept. of Transportation Safety Sunset Laws, 1973-1978 (Box 74, Folder 1-3)